Something funny is happening in WINTER KILLS. Take it seriously!
Winter Kills is a drama, mystery, thriller film directed by William Richert.
The younger brother of an assassinated US President is led down a rabbit hole of
conspiracies and dead ends after learning of a man claiming to be the real shooter.
Nick Kegan, played by Jeff Bridges.
Pa Kegan, played by John Huston.
John Cerruti, played by Anthony Perkins.
Joe Diamond, played by Eli Wallach.
Z.K. Dawson, played by Sterling Hayden.
Emma Kegan, played by Dorothy Malone.
Winter Kills is a 1979 satirical black comedy thriller film written and directed
by William Richert, based on the 1974 novel by Richard Condon.
Inspired by the John F.
Kennedy assassination conspiracy, its ensemble cast includes Jeff Bridges, John Huston, Anthony Perkins, Eli Wallach, Richard Boone,
Toshirō Mifune, Sterling Hayden, Dorothy Malone, Belinda Bauer, Ralph Meeker, Elizabeth Taylor, Berry Berenson and Susan Walden.
The tone is intense and lighthearted and emotional.